[
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Single point of failure\"",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Fixed Capacity\"",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"HDFS file system\"",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Support multi-tenancy\"",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Location dependent\"",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"FAT file system\"",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Heterogeneous clients\"",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Fixed IP-addresses\"",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Improved utilization\"",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Redundancy\"",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Private hardware\"",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Categorize the following characteristics: \"Improved scalability\"",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Cloud", "Not cloud"]
  }
]
